[
    {
        "question": "👊🏻👨🏻‍🦲🦸🏻‍♂️",
        "response": "سايتما"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍎✍🏻📓",
        "response": "لايت"
    },
    {
        "question": "🫎🧑🏻‍⚕️❄️ ",
        "response": "تشوبر"
    },
    {
        "question": "🔥👱🏻‍♂️❄️ ",
        "response": "تودوروكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧑‍🍳🦵🏻🚬",
        "response": "سانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐗⚔️👦🏻",
        "response": "اينوسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "💀🎸👑",
        "response": "بروك"
    },
    {
        "question": "🔥🧑🏻‍🚒🚒",
        "response": "شينزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "💇🏻‍♀️🌸🙍🏻‍♀️ ",
        "response": "ساكورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "👨🏻‍🦰🏜️🏺 ",
        "response": "غارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦊🍜🍥 ",
        "response": "ناروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍀📖👿 ",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "☀️🗡️😮‍💨",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐍😛🔬",
        "response": "اوروتشيماو"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚫⚪☁️",
        "response": "زيتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🤡🃏👦🏻",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧑🏻🔙🧑",
        "response": "تاكيميتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "👒🍖🏴‍☠",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🥪👦🏻👊🏻",
        "response": "ماش"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧛🏻‍♂️☀️👿",
        "response": "موزان"
    },
    {
        "question": "⛓️👀🧑",
        "response": "كورابيكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏴‍☠️⚓︎🤥 ",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚔️🌊🧑🏻",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚔️🔥🧑",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚔️💨🧑🏻",
        "response": "سانيمي"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚔️🧑🏻☁️",
        "response": "توكيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚔️👩🏻🦋 ",
        "response": "شينوبو"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚔️👩🏻🩷 ",
        "response": "ميتسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧑🏻🪨⚔️",
        "response": "جيومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚔️🧑🏻🎇🎆",
        "response": "تينغن"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧑🎩🔥",
        "response": "سابو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐜👑💪🏻",
        "response": "ميريوم"
    },
    {
        "question": "😈🏺",
        "response": "جيوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎭 👩🏻👁️",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "😈🎻👩🏻 ",
        "response": "ناكيمي"
    },
    {
        "question": "😎🥶❄️👁️",
        "response": "غوجو"
    },
    {
        "question": "😊👩🏻💰",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "💰☠️👑🏴‍☠️",
        "response": "روجر"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧑‍🍳🦵🏻🚬",
        "response": "سانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "👦🏻🛹⚡",
        "response": "كيلوا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🌙🦑🧑🏻‍🏫 ",
        "response": "كورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐸🍻🔞 ",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍀📖👿 ",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎤🦑⚔️ ",
        "response": "كيلر بي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🕵🏻‍♂️💊🛹 ",
        "response": "كونان"
}
]
